[{"answer": "Believe me I didn't see anything", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Boyfriend-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "No, did you", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Oh, they don't have phones out of town? Why do people say they're too busy. Too busy. Pick up a phone!! It takes two minutes. How can you be too busy", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Boyfriend-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I can't call here, it's a coffee shop. I mean what am I going to say to him", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "well it's a dog leg left, so I play the hook right? .. hold on there's another call.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Boyfriend-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Who are you talkin about", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Boyfriend-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "You know what, bad mistake my mistake do me a favor go back to the other lane", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Boyfriend-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Get out", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "That's it GET OUT!", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Boyfriend-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Get out of my cab", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Get out", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Boyfriend-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Wa, I'm not getting out of this cab", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Why? I'll tell you why..", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Boyfriend-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "No, you can't tell it .", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Let me tell it .", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Boyfriend-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "You always tell it .", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Agai", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Boyfriend-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Back and to the left Back and to the lef", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Who paid", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Boyfriend-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Split it. Pretty good. Talk about game six", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "So then as I was getting out of the car, ..", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Boyfriend-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Hi my friend", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Hi my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Boyfriend-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "What date? It's a GUY", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "No, don't cancel it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Boyfriend-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Well, frankly it is", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Friday night? Nothin', ... now", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Boyfriend-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Fasten your seat belts. we're goin' to see the baby", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Okay, wanna come with me and see the baby", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Boyfriend-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Come on, if you don't see the baby now you're never gonna see i", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Come on, if you don't see the baby now you're never gonna see i", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Boyfriend-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "All right  ", "qsentId": 34}]